Hello, David.
Can folks hear me?
I can hear you, but you're not saying hi to me.
Oh, okay.
Hi, Wade.
Hi, Akritas.
How are you?
I'm all right.
Well, you know, whenever I say hi to Dave, he's always like cheery and says I'm doing fine.
Whenever I say hi to you, you bring me down with like tales of woe.
Negative person.
I can bring you down with tales of woe.
But oh, yeah, but dude, when you bring me down to tales of woe, then I have to go get alcohol.
I have to like question the meaning of life.
Are you saying I need to get better at my downtroddenness?
I could take lessons.
Man, can't you just let somebody have something?
No.
Everybody needs to be as miserable as me all the time.
No, I meant let him be better at doing this than you.
He's got more experience.
Russell asks about you all the time, Wade.
Well, tell him to, you know, come join me at lunch on Thursdays or something.
He knows what the deal is.
I don't think he's going to join you at lunch.
No, he did once, the day after we all got laid off, like Brutals and me and such.
That was a fun day.
Probably more fun.
I just want to say something.
We have very definitions of the term and understandings of the term fun.
No, Wade was very happy to be laid off.
No, I was.
I was on the way out.
They could have let me go for free.
It was basically free money that he got that we could have given him no money and said we gave him extra money.
Yes.
And unemployment even.
So even extra government money.
Oh, yeah.
It was great.
Yeah.
Oh, Caroline thought that it would, you know, entice me to come back in a couple of months.
And nope.
How is Brutals doing?
I don't know.
I haven't.
He's, he's a, he's always been kind of a mess.
He's, I think he's still roaming.
Like, I think he tried living in Austin and then he had one summer there and he said, fuck that.
Really hot there.
Yeah, but he was still coming back here periodically for like his dentist or something.
It was just like, of all the things to come back to the Bay Area for.
Especially an Englishman to care that much about his dental work.
Oh, oh, oh, man.
No, that's fair.
But I haven't heard from him in about a year.
It's probably fine.
Like he's exceedingly private.
It's hard to get anything out of him.
Yeah, he always was.
Oh, well, 20.
That's supposed to be.
Oh, yeah.
I should probably open up the websites in advance.
No, Caroline's gone.
Yeah, I heard she finally got the axe.
Yep, she did.
She said, she told me afterward, she's just like, hey, I guess I just couldn't play the political game at Roku.
I'm like, isn't that your job?
I mean, talk about reducing people to their essence and like, no love, man.
No, but that's what she told me.
She said that she just couldn't keep up with the politics or something.
And I'm like, that's director and up.
Like, that's pretty much all you do, I thought.
She lasted a couple of years.
I mean, she had like five or six good years and she, I had nothing against her.
Once Scott was out.
Oh, Scott?
Oh, he left, I assume, right?
He didn't get fired down.
Yeah, once Scott was out, that was kind of she couldn't find her place anymore.
Yeah, well, that's a shame.
Scott was really good.
Who's in his position now?
Bank attached.
Oh, sorry.
No, not Vankatish.
I was thinking of Vinayak.
I like Vankatez.
Vinayak was.
Vinayak's gone.
Oh, thank Christ.
Oh, my God.
That guy once just stopped me in the middle of a meeting.
He's like, if it takes 45 milliseconds to go to frame, how can we do 60 frames a second?
I'm just like, I don't have the crayons, dude.
The crayons.
Jesus Christ.
He's gone.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
I hated him.
Rom, Rom Marty?
No.
Jerome's gone.
Sheldon's gone.
A lot of these names I don't really know.
They didn't cross me negatively.
Hey, Gary.
Hi, Gary.
Hello.
They keep telling me I'm doing a good job, though.
No one wants to fire me.
I think you did fine.
You got QT out of the build.
That's huge.
I'm sure you've done more since then, but that was huge.
Like, that was a complete unnecessary dependency.
I just want to say.
Yes.
If Dave's performance as Vukradin is any indication, he has definitely mastered the art of naive, being able to pretend to not understand politics while playing the game very well.
I mean, that is politics.
I just want to say that.
I think Vukradin has decided that he needs to be allies with everyone because the more allies he has, the more people are going to come, listen to him play.
That's how he's happy to have anyone listen to him.
You know, he could also just make his own family army of audience, or all audience.
Wait a second.
That means that he's aligning with what's her name?
You didn't read my summary, did you?
No, no, no, no.
He's thinking.
No, at the end of the last session, I was like, yeah, I guess I could go do this thing for Soma.
It'd be good to be allies with everybody.
I mean, I'm just trying to keep balance.
Yeah, let's make allies with everyone.
Why not?
We don't know who's fucking with the Whispering Wood.
I need money, and I need people to come listen to me play.
I was just saying that it's not any unethical money.
Adabra said that she recently thought you were one of her kind is because you were for the music.
Oh, she thinks he's an artist.
I think I'm for the fans.
Oh, well, you know, she thought you were for the music.
That's fine.
We don't have to tell her that.
Wait, are you sure you're for the fans and not the music?
I think I might be more for the fans, actually.
He just wants to be famous.
But when they listen to the music you want, or when they listen to the music, I know, I know.
It's this character arc I'm going through.
Do I want to go pop?
Do I want to sell out?
I like the idea of him challenging.
How much of a sellout am I going to be?
I love the idea.
He suddenly discovered that when he plays with Velfanar.
Yeah.
Hey, I started playing with Velfanar, right?
Things are looking up.
Yes.
So now this is a nice drow.
I don't know.
What's wrong with the Drow ally?
She plays pretty well.
Hold on.
She has her own version of music.
It's a combination of Lathander choral music and brings in the Drow metal.
Is that the Indian?
Lex Coralum.
Maleficum.
Death Medal.
Sounds cursed.
She's not just into playing Drow music.
This is a mixture.
Pop thing.
As long as it's not unethical.
It's not unethical to be popped.
It's just pathetic.
Is it unethical to sell out your craft for money, though?
Oh, no, it's just pathetic.
Okay.
Cool.
I'm on board 100%.
Did Akritas?
No, he's alive.
Yeah, I'm just trying to think right now.
All right.
Talk to Soma's Soma's Quest.
Soma's Quest.
The whole of Phandalin needs this.
This could spread.
I'm on board, man.
I'm with you, friend.
Yeah, the trees will pay for our ribbon for us.
The Whispering Wood.
Adabra, the midwife we saved earlier, asked you to save the Whispering Wood from a magical blight.
Yep.
Really, from the interventionist causing said blight.
They come to my concert.
Maybe.
I mean, maybe they're the orcs who attacked us.
I don't know.
Oh, yeah, those guys.
Who are these?
Who are these people?
I don't know.
We don't know.
This has been extremely, this module or whatever is extremely light on the pre-quest details.
Like, go fix the lighthouse.
What's wrong with it?
Oh, something.
Something.
You'll find it.
Something's wrong with it.
What's wrong with those forums?
Oh, blight.
You know, we could probably ask for more details.
We did.
We don't get it.
We're trying to be more on the down low with our.
Yeah, so we decided to not ask detail and to just head out because Vukradin was all about the conspiracy theories last time.
Yeah, still not so sure about Sir Kaelen.
The letter did not help.
But I want to be allies with everyone.
I want him to come into my concerts.
So, you know, if he comes to your concert, Adabra comes to your concert, the Zhentarim come to the concert as long as.
Well, I don't know the Zhentarim.
Let me ask you a question.
If Vukradin is paid by the Zhentarim, does that wash?
I don't know.
That's stolen money.
No, is it?
You made it awesome.
Do you know the origins?
Harpers, on the other hand, they're legit.
They're good people.
I don't think I'm going to get used to this new Vukradin after the betrayal of the Harpers.
Oh, yeah, right.
But that's a previous campaign.
That's a different character.
Different characters.
Well, actually, an old man who might have looked like Orsick.
Yeah.
Orsick's father.
Orsick the wise.
Orsick.
All right.
Orsick father.
Let me just see if he's awesome.
All right, I need to open up something.
There it is.
Where is my.
I need to add this, don't I?
Oh, my staff came alive in the other.
God damn it.
I hate Google Chat.
All right.
Okay.
So head off to the Whispering Wood.
And as you approach the Whispering Wood, I need a quick, as you approach the edge of the Whispering Wood.
Let's see.
Description here.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
The Whispering Wood looks kind of normal to you.
It's kind of like, okay, if you're kind of staring at it, there doesn't seem to be anything odd about it.
You don't see any blight.
It just appears, I'm assuming somebody rolled investigations, insights.
Nature check.
You have your new staff, don't forget.
I do.
And I need to.
I was actually trying to pull that up.
I was going to ask, I should probably mark it as a tune, shouldn't I?
Yeah, and you probably need to put it in.
You probably need to mark one attunement spot and cut and paste those attributes I said.
Right.
I was literally in the middle of doing that as you were talking.
Yeah.
It's still nature checked thrown.
So, you know.
Nature check thrown.
Well, you definitely sense something is very off.
Guys, something is off.
But you're not quite sure.
What you do notice is that it is off, but it's not.
There's nothing natural.
There's something
strangely green and too few spots.
So let me ask you a question.
Do you tend towards the naturalist side?
So since you tend towards the naturalist side, to be quite honest, you don't really notice anything that is off.
You're kind of surprised that Soma would, that Adabra would say it's that it would say it's there's some kind of blight.
So it's just, it's just more of a vague sense of unease and not any like clear sense of like rotting trees or yeah, you're just kind of like there.
You do sense a blight, but you don't see it anywhere.
All this weird green of the overt bright, you know, like there's not even all that much like slime around.
I mean, like, it's really weird.
Trees thrive in light, right?
Like you, like you, Velfanar.
I don't think you understand the concept of what Velfanar does if you think she thrives in light.
Well, she enjoys the pain.
Yes, gloriously painful.
That's right.
I mean, that's a type of thriving.
The thing I've been wondering is: does Velfanar like, you know, is she like a...
Why has she not resorted to the stabbing herself and healing herself?
Is there some...
You don't think she does that?
You think she doesn't do that?
I just want to know if she does.
Just like a party trip before bed each night.
I deliberately made sure that she was quite pierced.
Okay.
Let me see.
I need a battle map.
All right.
Okay, this will do fine.
Okay.
Discern corruption.
Hello.
Sorry.
Now, as I'm cutting and pasting everything in, may as well throw that into the mix.
All right.
Can I mark?
I don't know how to mark this attuned.
I just have to remember that in my head.
All right.
Okay, come on.
What now?
I'm just trying to find the monster, and it's not like animal.
Is that what I'm moving forward?
All right, fine.
I'll just have to drop the token in here.
Sorry, my bad.
Heck is going.
All right.
Oh, geez.
So we're still on the world map.
Yeah, I know, I know.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sometimes you forget.
No, no, that's fair.
That's fair.
But thank you for reminding me.
All right.
Okay.
So now I will.
Can you tell me where on the world map we entered?
Yes, you entered into the Whispering Wood.
Okay.
Oh, right.
I remember it was marked on there.
Yeah.
So if you see where you guys are, like, there's a little red thing, red lettering.
The Whispering Wood.
Yeah.
Yes.
Whispering Wood.
Yes, Whispering Wood.
Okay.
It's very near.
Yeah.
Okay.
So.
Looks like it's on like a one-hour hike from Phandalin.
It's a one-hour hike.
Yeah.
It's a pat, it's a, it's an area of wooded area that's called the Whispering Wood.
It's, you know, kind of like between valleys and whatnot.
It's kind of a weird sort of dense forest area.
And there's a stag here.
Yeah, but let me give you the description.
Hold on.
All right.
Does anybody have speak with animals?
I do.
Of course I do.
Excellent.
All right.
So the stag suddenly is standing in front of you.
Yeah, I know that this is probably me, unless it's another Krabby that can talk.
What?
Nope.
All you, man.
Yeah.
And I'm just going to show you.
I forgot.
Aw, such a pretty boy.
What you notice is that the flag, it's a majestic stag, except its fur is shimmering, flickering that phases in and out.
As you look at, as you look at, roll a nature check, perception check.
Nature perception.
Whichever, whichever nature, insight, investigation, arcano, whichever ones you want.
19.
All right.
Oh, yeah.
23.
This is my wheelhouse.
Yes, yes.
Soma has discovered that this stag is caught between dimensions.
That can't be good.
No.
And so all of a sudden, it flickers.
And she also notices that its antlers are kind of like embedded in, you know, like those four-dimensional things that are embedded in three-dimensional space.
Oh, like the hypercube, you mean?
Where it's like it's constantly changing a 3D shape.
Yes, it's constantly changing its presence in our universe.
Right.
Or our plane or whatever.
And it teleports 15 feet.
Okay, I don't think I need a staff to detect an unnatural blight here.
I think that that is unnatural.
Hey, do you want to talk to the stag?
I do want to talk to the stag.
So I burn a slice slot.
You're going to burn a slice pauselot.
Okay.
Well, I assume.
I mean, I.
Yeah, here's me a second.
Oh, we have long rested, I assume, since last thing.
My spell slots are not.
Hold on.
Everybody's long rested.
There we go.
But I did.
Yes, you did.
Hello?
Oh, sorry.
Wrong button.
Stop trying to kill everything.
What did you turn on?
That was the wrong button.
You rolled initiative.
Throw out my draggers.
Just talk to him.
Put them on.
Chill, man.
Chill.
Go play some music.
Okay, so how does that speak with animals work?
For the duration, I can comprehend and verbally communicate with beasts and can use any influence action skill on them.
Most beasts are really boring and have nothing to say, but at minimum, the beast can give you information.
Okay, so the beast sort of says, okay, so what is it that you would like to ask the beast?
Are you okay?
I think I'm just more concerned about its welfare watching it do this sort of bizarre existence.
It pauses and goes, I was okay until you walked into my territory.
Why are you in my territory?
Get out of my territory.
We're just passing through.
We mean no harm.
We just noticed that you seem out of sorts.
I don't know what you mean.
I'm completely.
I am completely now.
And so the stag sort of looks at you and sort of you can roll an insight to see where the boundaries of its territory are.
I can try.
Let's see.
Where is it?
Under I, wouldn't it be?
Yes.
I think, do I get an advantage on that as well?
You got it, man.
15.
Sure.
All right.
I get insight on wisdom checks in natural territories, which this would be, or advantage on.
Yes, it would be.
Then this would be.
Yes, go ahead, toss it again.
It's a wisdom-based role.
So there we go.
So I got a 20 now.
Oh, yeah.
So you're definitely able to identify.
This is a Soma quest.
It's going to be easy for her.
We're all just along for the ride.
Kind of.
We'll try to make it quick.
I got my daggers.
Which side of the boundary is his, the north or the south?
The side he's on.
Well, he didn't start there.
He teleported there.
No, he started.
You know, it's true.
But it's because you guys, like, you know, he's got his boundary.
Yeah.
Brewberry, can you back off a little?
Just, you know.
This guy, he's.
Brew, come on over here.
Brew, could you back up a little?
Just give the stag some privacy.
Sure.
There.
All right.
We've cleared your territory.
Is there something weird going on, though?
I'm not used to seeing stags teleport around and shimmer like you do.
The stag goes, looks at this, looks and goes, oh.
And then he teleports again and leaves an after image behind where he was.
Sorry, I forgot to mention that last time.
So he sort of leaves an it's like a displacer beast.
Yeah.
Yeah, blink dog.
Blink dagger.
Blink stag is perfect.
And then after like a few seconds, it disappears.
And he goes, I am.
He goes, hmm.
I do.
I must.
This is very weak.
He does pause and says, yes, things have not been normal for some time.
Come on over and just kind of follow him around his edge of the cage.
Some time.
Do you have any vague idea how much time?
And what do you mean by things have not been normal?
Well, I used to just be able to walk and prance and eat the vegetables.
And now I can blink.
And my horns are different.
My antlers are different.
They're different every time I look at them.
Exactly.
Do you know how difficult it is to go through the forest with your antlers?
I can't.
I wouldn't know.
I don't have antlers.
Well, imagine if you had a shell that changed shape all the time.
It would just be awkward.
It would.
Do you remember anything weird happening that led to all this?
Did you drink some weird water, eat some mushrooms?
No, the whole forest has gotten weird.
It's almost as if everything has changed.
That's what they tell us in town as well, that things have gotten a little strange out here.
Yes, everything has changed.
It pauses.
It pauses and goes, but he looks at you and says, Do you have anything to eat?
God, what a one gift for some good berries.
Do we have anything in our inventory for a stag?
We have some octopus or something?
We have some green mushroom rations.
Yeah, purple.
Oh, I forget.
Purple fermentable mushrooms.
Yeah, deer.
Well, those could turn into potions, right?
And shark meat.
I think he's an herbivore, right?
Yeah, he's an herbivore.
Go with the green mushroom rations.
Yeah, yeah.
Have some mushroom rations.
All right.
So the deer says, well, it all started in the center of the forest.
In the center.
Yes.
He goes, he points you in the general rough direction.
And then he says, and there were some other nice people who came here.
Yes.
Describe them.
What did they do?
Who were they?
What did they look like?
Well, there was a druid.
They were very nice.
They spoke to me too.
We druids do that.
Yes.
It's a party trick.
They spoke to me too, and they asked, and everything started to, and they said they would fix it, but they haven't.
Do you know how they tried?
Did you give them any pointers to fixing it?
No, I was too busy eating and trying to tell them to get out of my home.
What are the odds that the problem is inside your territory, and we might need to come look in?
Well, why don't you go to the center first?
And if it's not there, you can come and you can come back.
All right.
Or you could try to persuade him to, or you could try to persuade him.
No, I think it's fine to check the center first and come check back.
He's probably not going far.
How far are we from the center?
A few survival checks away.
Monster.
That's all right.
Advantage on all of those.
Right, right.
All right.
Then I guess we trek on towards the center.
Yes.
I got you, Fam.
What did you get?
Survival.
23.
All right.
Okay, here we go.
So you see a dense thicket of brambles with leaves that pulse with unnatural colors, sometimes glowing, sometimes withering to black.
Torch them.
That might actually be the legit cause here case here.
I don't know.
I may as well burn the one check along the way.
Yeah.
So just.
Oh, this isn't the center yet.
This is the first survival check.
Yes.
This is yes here.
There's a dense thicket of.
Okay.
Nobody has fireball yet, do you?
No, nobody has fireball.
No, but we have smaller fires.
I mean, we could just do it old school, right?
Like just a regular old fire.
Sounds like it's combat.
Yeah, yeah.
Anything to be discerned from them?
I mean, like, I assume they look quite unnatural.
Like, yeah, I finally blew a roll.
Okay, so did you try to discern something?
Well, I tried to do a nature check on it as, you know, they're brambles, aren't they?
Here we go.
They looked like that.
So you did a nature check.
They look like that I see a non-thing.
Yeah, we don't see anything.
Oh, wait, there we go.
I see.
Whoa.
They look like giant anuses made of branches.
So again, there's like sort of like a bizarre sort of quality to them that makes them look somewhat less than normal.
Again, at this point in time, you're correctly discerning that whatever this blight may or may not be, there seems to be some sort of planar leakage, bleeding.
Like this is not.
Yeah, that's not normal.
Yes.
And as you approach within 10 feet, it strikes you.
Oh, good.
Good, good, good.
Let's go.
You were going to torch it, right?
Well, I was going to go up and expect it, and I got whacked.
So, yeah, I think they need to get burned.
Do I have to defense or anything?
What happens?
Okay, hold on.
Oh, sure.
Do the brambles grapple me?
Let's just roll for initiative.
We're literally fighting a thicket.
Yes.
All right.
Switch tabs.
Some is a 12.
All right.
So what I got.
No, 13.
Okay, or let me just
thicket.
Are you really going to call it a thicket?
I need to call it something.
Something.
No, I think it's fine.
I think it's appropriate.
I just.
Yeah.
All right.
Next up, you know, magic missile of the darkness or something.
All right, there.
Okay.
Is there just one thicket?
16, 15.
Yes, it's just one big thicket.
52 hit points.
And be with a blunt weapon.
You got an initiative for the thicket?
Yeah, the rolls with the, gets no bonuses, so whatever.
It should be a zero.
Do you think it has no bonus?
No, I mean, it's dexterity.
Okay.
That just sounded awful.
I think it will not get to attack, is my prediction.
All right, Velfina.
All right.
She can start with probably Sacred Flame.
That seems appropriate.
Seems like a good choice.
Isn't that technically radiant, but still fine?
Technically, radiant.
Yeah.
But it has a save DC13.
All right.
I need to roll.
It has no bonuses because, again, like I said, it doesn't have any dexterity.
No bonus or a negative bonus?
No bonus.
Made it save three dodges.
No, actually, what happens is suddenly the plane shifts just enough.
Oh, yeah.
It's planar shifting, dodging.
Okay, yeah.
That tracks.
No, it wasn't so much it was, but the whole environment sort of shifts.
It itself doesn't do anything.
But we're just like stable through all this, right?
So far.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
So Bruperi will move in closer and then does he move in within 10 feet?
To exactly 10 feet.
Okay, cool.
Just checking.
Because he doesn't have to be closer.
All right.
Because he's got reach or whatever.
Yes, he's got the all-important reach.
Let's see.
Why is this not giving me an attack pop-up today?
Okay.
Okay, so you are, in fact,
attacked by some thorny tendrils.
Oh.
Actually, Soma should have been attacked by thorny tendrils.
Well, yeah, I thought that was how the combat started.
So forgiven I forgot to do that.
Yeah, go ahead and roll one on me.
Yeah, okay.
Plus four to hit.
Aren't you glad I blew that on my saving throw?
Yes.
I did not want to be crit.
Oh, wow, that still sucks.
That's a hit.
All right.
You take seven points of damage.
And you take you take seven points of piercing damage plus three necrotic, and you must also make a DC12 constitution saving throw or be poisoned.
Constitution.
All right.
And there we go.
I get poisoned.
Yes.
All right.
That means you have disadvantage on some things.
On some things.
All right.
Back to Brewberry then.
I don't understand why, but it appears that virtual tabletop does not like Beyond 20 does not like to have
more than one character open.
Swear you can't do it.
It's not letting me just roll the weapon attack.
Are you sure the mod just didn't disconnect?
No, you've rolled other things, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, I will do this very manually.
There, I there, dude, the poison condition there for assault.
You think a lot of us are getting poisoned, huh?
All right.
So I assume that's a hit.
Yes, a DC12.
Whatever I put there, 12, yes.
Yeah.
Plus 6.
Sorry.
It should be 1D
12 plus 6.
Okay.
1D 10 plus 6.
And you aren't raging or anything, right?
16.
Yeah.
Okay.
16 points of damage.
Could you mark that down or I'll mark it down?
I will not.
Thank you.
All right.
Soma.
Yeah.
So the poison condition runs out at the end of your turn, just so you know.
Oh, it's literally just one round.
Well, either way, we're going to wild shape.
Give me the bear icon when you get a chance.
All right.
Bear icon.
That's going to be worth a burned slot.
And then.
So I have disadvantage on all attacks.
Huh?
Brat-large brown bear, yeah.
I thought.
Or just brown bear.
Oh, I know what it is.
The giant toad soma, but we haven't done the giant toad.
I've done bear before.
I've done bear plenty of time.
Yeah, no, no.
This is just me.
This is me whining to myself, not to you.
Oh, there we go.
Copy of brown bear.
All right.
Once I use the fourth shape, you're going to have to keep me honest.
Nameplate Soma.
Bears.
Controlled by all players.
Save changes.
All right.
There you go.
One Soma Brown Bear.
All right.
Multi-attack, but it's going to be a disadvantage.
There's going to be two misses, I'm sure.
Let's go.
Public roll.
Yep, that's a miss.
And then the multi-second.
That's a hit.
It's a hit.
14 hits.
What is it?
Piercing or slashing?
That's slashing.
All right, so that's real damage.
That should be real damage, so 26 now.
Mukrudin.
All right.
Let's start with.
And then poison is expired now, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Unsettling words, roll a 1d6.
Creature must subtract the number rolled from the next saving throw it makes.
Okay.
So it's got a minus two on a saving.
Say creature because it's a plant.
Why is a plant not a creature?
Why is plant not a creature?
Okay, that's a good question.
Is a plant a creature?
I mean, I think creature is like a generic term.
Yes, not an air creature object.
It's not like a pedestal.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, I.
It's not a gazebo.
It could be turned into a gazebo.
Just for the record, I know what a gazebo is.
I've told you the gazebo.
I've told you about my son and the gazebo story, right?
Yes, many times.
Not me, but we'll save it for another day.
All right.
I'll bore you at another time.
All right, yes.
So minus two.
Mm-hmm.
You mock them.
Mock the plants.
DC13 wisdom save.
Or DC15.
Oh, because he's got, yeah, minus two.
Not a minus two.
So equivalent of a DC15.
Is it a wisdom?
Oh, my God.
So that's like that's a 19 or a 20.
Well, it's a 10% chance.
Ah, you blew that one.
Okay.
You take four damage and you have disadvantage on your attack.
I never thought of a creature like this having disadvantage.
Okay.
You now have.
I'll take the four off.
All right.
Regenerates for five hit points.
So 27.
Yep.
And I assume it's going to try to attack?
Yes.
Just a bear.
I belong here.
Don't mess with me.
Okay, but it has disadvantage.
Sure.
All right.
It will.
The bear is, so I guess it'll probably go after.
I was just joking, but sure.
I don't look out of place.
Well, no, you don't because you shifted in your planar sensibilities.
Let's see.
I will.
The only two targets are Brewberry and
all right.
Brewberry it is.
Actually, it does two attacks, so it'll attack twice.
First one is disadvantage, second is normal then.
Okay, so we will.
First one is 2D20.
Eat low one.
Let me see the bottom.
Yeah, beyond 20 is definitely not working for me anymore.
Oh.
That's a bummer.
Plus four.
Another one of my friends who's playing Dungeons and Dragons.
Oh, this might explain why another one of my friends was having a problem.
When they had two character sheets open, the one of the two did not, the attack rolls did not work.
Oh, because he has Brewberry and Velfina.
Yeah, that's weird.
Like, I have.
Well, I don't have two character sheets open.
I have a monster sheet and a character sheet, and they both work.
I've had two open in the past.
It works fine.
No, this has definitely been a new behavior that I've seen with my cousin.
And right now I'm getting no buttons on either character after reloading the taps.
Including logging into roll 20 again.
Did you try uninstalling the device thing and reinstalling it?
The plugin.
Yeah.
The extension, yeah.
Yeah, I can do that.
So you got a 10, a 10 on the first one.
That's a miss.
Yep.
All right.
Second attack.
And then the second attack is on Soma.
No, it's on Brewberry because it's kind of mindless that way.
13.
I think that's a miss, right?
Also a miss.
I think it's a miss on either one of us.
Yep.
Okay.
Back to the top.
Yes.
Okay.
Valfina.
All right.
Assume that we're going to do this sacred flame again?
Yes.
The deck save.
Yeah.
I can.
Oh, no.
I rolled a 17.
Ah, Christ.
It's really good at dodging sacred flames through its planarness.
Does that work?
Yes, it does.
Yeah, we see it.
We see cool.
I rolled the 17.
All right, then.
Next, I guess we got Brewberry.
Yes.
Ah, and the button is not showing up.
Reload this character sheet and see if it does it now.
Ah, no.
Okay, two different browsers.
Whatever.
I'm kidding.
I have that here.
What the heck is that?
Okay.
Next thing we're going to do is we're going to reach for the dice.
Yeah.
Crits.
Okay.
All right.
So we do 1010
plus 6.
And then I have another D10 for crit.
Yes.
And then my strength damage is not edit twice.
Is that correct?
Yes, that is correct.
Okay, so 17.
And I assume I don't get to cleave because it's still one creature, right?
Yes, yes, it's one creature.
All right.
Okay, it's down to 10.
Yep.
All right, I got this.
I think.
Bring it home, bear.
Let's go.
I'm just going to roll them both without looking.
That's a mess.
That's 14 damage.
That'll finish it.
That'll do it.
All right.
Good job, team.
It temporarily.
Yeah, it's going to regenerate, isn't it?
Yes, if you want to go past it, you should go past it now.
Yeah, I get that sense.
We should continue our trek.
We set it on fire as we go.
Yeah, I think that's worth doing.
Well, you don't want to burn down the whole forest.
Like, how much kindling is around it?
As a forest, I assume there's plenty of kindling.
Yes.
Yeah, I'd really like not to burn down the whole forest.
You don't want to declare a forest fire?
No, no, I'm not a.
What do you think Adabra would say?
I think she would consider us interventionists.
We're just destroying it.
We rescued the Whispering Wood.
That's right.
It didn't survive the rescuing, but we rescued it.
Yeah, and I think Adabra would not be pleased.
You're going to have to let me know how much time passes because I have an hour in bear form.
Yeah, okay.
All right.
I think going to the center of the forest is not going to take an hour.
It only took us an hour to get to the right, right?
But I'm just informing the GM of that.
Yeah, thank you for that.
All right.
Another survival check, I assume.
Yes.
Oh, wow.
Well, you're not the only one in the party, you know.
All right.
Yeah.
Somebody.
I can't do this as a bear, apparently.
Vukradin is quite convinced.
Brewberry.
Velfina.
Oh, yay!
I don't know that any of those are good enough.
Oh, actually, that was Brewberry's, not Velfina's.
Oh, yeah.
He got two Brewberries.
That one, last one, was supposed to be the Velfina with the plus three.
So that was.
So 13.
13 for Velfina.
They both showed up as Brewberry with the same Brewberry bonus.
That's what I got.
All right.
So, you know, Brewberry.
So, so, Velfina, so you're now at a point of conflict where Vukradin is quite convinced he knows which way to go.
I don't know anything.
Does he defer to Velfina?
I just know that, like, I don't discern the correct path of that.
Yeah.
And apparently, I lost my senses as a bear.
Right.
Okay.
All right.
So you avoid getting lost.
And
all right.
As you're walking through the forest, you hear distant howls which echo unnaturally, sometimes overlapping or out of sync with the environment.
Hey guys, this is kind of creepy.
It's like the Blair Witch, dude.
So nothing's going to happen, and everybody's going to get pissed and walk out of the theater?
Oh, dude, that's not.
I liked that movie.
You did?
I did.
There's nothing wrong with it.
I'm just joking.
It does take a lot of hate, though.
Anyway, so we hear this echoing weird kickoff.
Huh?
What?
They all died.
Nothing is going to happen.
Every single one of them.
They die off camera, though, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
So as you're bouncing around, a dire wolf.
Sort of working.
Good.
A dire wolf.
Oh, man.
Why'd I do bear instead of wolf?
Because you.
And think, how long does speak with animals last?
10 minutes.
I checked it.
More than 10 minutes.
10 minutes have elapsed.
Ah, Christ.
So I can't talk to him without tossing a spell slot.
That's just a family, right?
We don't need to mess with a family.
It's a family of wolves, or it's a singular wolf.
It's a dire wolf with six wolves.
I only see five, which is terrifying enough.
There's the sixth.
Do they look like you know?
I'm about to give you that.
I'm about to show you a picture.
I had fun putting this adventure.
I hope you guys are at least creeped by it.
Only on Fireball.
Yeah, I know.
That's what Fireball was made for.
This exact encounter.
That is true.
Cleave.
What?
I dropped all my.
I dropped my area of effect spell.
I guess.
I'm not regretting that.
I did.
Oh, did you have an area of sleep or something?
I do have sleep, yeah.
Sleep's not as powerful as it used to be, though.
It's powerful in different ways, though.
I mean, if you could sleep like four of the little wolflings, it'd be fine.
All right.
So you should see these wolves here.
Yeah, it doesn't look good.
Yes.
Roll for initiative.
Hold on.
We can't talk to them.
I don't like being attacked.
18.
Yeah.
All right.
He's just going, guns blazing.
Okay.
So the wolves.
We got to save this robe for Adabra.
We can't just murder everyone.
Come to my concert.
She can bring the emerald enclave in.
All right.
Where's my Selma initiative from her?
Come on, roll.
Oh, jeez.
What a time to roll a 20.
Did you roll Selma?
Did you roll a 20?
I rolled a 20 on initiative.
I did not want to.
That's probably not something you wanted.
Huh?
Yes.
All right.
Let's see.
I can't cast much except like Moonbeam in animal form, can I?
Moonbeam's useful.
It is, but it's.
I have a trick with my sleeve too.
As do I.
I'm just trying to figure out like what I.
Yeah, I think that's the only thing I can.
Yeah.
All right.
Wolf two.
So the wolves howl as a pack.
As they approach you, they howl as a pack.
And everyone must make a saving throw against fear, against wisdom saving throw.
Wisdom.
I'm going to count that as a natural and natural environment.
Yeah, that was a good time.
So just if anybody's frightened, tell me.
Vukradin looks scared.
Yeah.
All right.
So I put the Vukradin the.
So does this interface with rage in some way?
What do you mean, interface?
Does rage and fear interact in some way?
No, I don't think so.
Is Brewberry afraid?
I don't see his role.
No, I wasn't rolling.
At six.
Okay, to answer your question.
At sixth level, you can't be charmed or frightened while raging.
Not quite level six yet.
Yeah.
So it does intersect, but not at this level.
Okay.
All right.
Did anybody get affected?
Only Vukradin.
Vukradin.
Which is fine.
You don't need to move closer.
Yes.
Okay.
All right.
Wolf two.
Wolf two rushes in.
And let's see what their movement is.
Sorry.
Armor class.
Well, 40 feet.
Okay.
So he rushes.
He rushes at Vukradin.
Takes a bite at you.
Disadvantage, I assume.
Only if I attack.
Yes.
All right.
So it has a it bites you.
Doesn't it?
Yes.
AC16.
Okay.
All right.
And if let me just make sure I got this right.
Let's not do very much damage.
All right.
Are you a medium or smaller creature?
Medium.
You are knocked prone.
Okay.
How much damage?
Sorry.
Yes.
Five points of damage.
I'm not anyway.
It's fine.
All right.
All right, Selma.
Yeah.
Well, may as well try to protect a little bit.
Focus on the dire wolf.
Yeah, well, I'm going to put down a moon beam in front of everyone.
Oh, yeah, that works.
Yeah, so I need a five-foot radius circle, probably around there.
It is semi-permanent.
And so those guys are going to take.
I should cast.
You can move the beam each round, right?
Yes.
That's why I said it's like semi-permanent.
Yeah.
What is that?
How big is it?
It's five-foot radius, so 10 feet wide.
So it can at least hit these two, but it's not going to be able to move that.
I can.
First try.
Excellent.
I should actually see it in the sidebar thing, the side thing.
Should say area of effect templates when you click on the little magic book.
Let me double-check.
I've seen this before, but I could pull stuff out.
Oh, yeah.
Can I delete now?
I guess I didn't need you for that.
All right.
No, I'm just saying next time you can just do that.
Yeah.
Anyway, so that's the moon beam that's down there.
Those guys take the damage I chucked, which I have misplaced, and Constitution Save, yeah.
All right, Constitution Save.
The wolf blows it and dies.
Oh, they're that low.
Oh, I didn't even look at their HP.
That's not particularly challenging combat.
D20.
The other guy makes it.
So he takes five points.
Yeah.
All right, five points on Big Daddy.
32.
All right.
All right, Velfina, you're up.
I'm actually going to.
Sorry, I'm going to move up to give a little cover to people too.
No, that should be 22.
I don't know why it says 32.
It should be 22.
But the dire wolf.
Okay, dire wolf's down to 22 hit points.
No, he started off with 22, so he's down to 17.
Oh, okay.
So he's 22, and we did five, so he did 17.
Oh, this is nothing.
This is just, that was a waste of a spell.
All right.
No, it's good.
It's good use.
It's good.
Velfina.
I could have mauled that.
So she moves here and then she casts fairy fire on all five of those guys.
You don't need to do that.
They're 11 hit points.
Fine.
I mean, you can.
It's just.
They're not.
Okay.
Just as a side note, you can't cast spells while you're in wild shape.
You can cast Moonbeam when you're in wild shape.
Oh, I did not know that.
Right at the bottom, it says in bright red, like, says that right at the bottom of the spell.
Fair enough.
That's an exception, huh?
It is a circle of the moon spell, which is the specialization.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
That is the only spell I can cast in wild shape.
All right.
I like it.
Cool.
All right.
Who's next?
Anyway, I'm going to still fairy fire all those guys.
Okay.
Yeah, DC 13 deck save.
Yeah, so tell me which ones succeed.
Okay.
The only ones that fail are one and six.
Everybody else succeeds.
One and six failed, and four or five did succeeded.
Yeah.
Good.
For me.
I rolled well.
I will.
Drop a sleep on those three guys there.
Well, could you could I give you another one?
That would be nice.
Thank you.
You can also pull your own if you want.
You can have different colors.
I don't know.
This magic book you talked about.
Yeah, I was looking for the book, too.
I couldn't find it.
It's the third icon after the.
It's chat, then a palette, then a magic book in the top right.
I see it.
Oh, and this is where you have the party characters, too.
Yeah, yeah, that's where all the party characters.
You should even see your bear icon there.
I do.
Selma the bear, Selma the spider.
It's snapping snapping to the grid, though.
I like remove snap to grid.
Yeah, you hit alt and then place it wherever you want.
Oh, alt.
There.
That won't.
That will.
Okay, so the rule is 50%.
That's not 50%.
That's 25%.
Rule is 50%.
What rule?
The GM.
No, we went over this at the very beginning.
20 here.
Okay.
I don't understand.
No, it has to cover 50%.
It can't just be like a touch.
Well, forget it then.
You could get those two.
No.
It's a waste.
Okay.
When you get a subclass to get Fireball.
Yeah.
I'm not very excited about the capabilities of this.
I'm frightened, so I can't attack.
You can attack.
You just can't move closer.
I can't move closer.
If I attack, I have disadvantage.
Are you frightened by the wolves or the dire wolves or both?
He's frightened by the frightened wolves have caused the frightened condition.
So does that mean you can still attack the dire wolf normally?
Just with disadvantage.
No, it has it as a disadvantage.
With disadvantage.
Oh, like on all attacks.
Yeah.
Okay.
And I can't reach the dire wolf.
Yeah.
Great.
Hmm.
I don't know.
Do the spell you were going to do either way.
Well, I'm a little disappointed.
I've got very little here.
Throw a dagger.
Just take the disadvantage and deal with it.
There's this mockery on the dire wolf.
We'll drop the natural 20.
Yeah.
All right, whatever.
All right.
You are no longer.
No, no, that's not true.
No, that's not true.
All right.
Brewberry, you're up.
You remain frightened as long as they're alive.
Why is your arrow?
Six.
I've got a stuck arrow.
Okay.
So I'm going to attack six and then cleave into four.
All right.
Can't cleave into the big guy?
Clean up all these little guys.
Okay.
And then immediately my attack button's not working.
I think.
How about that?
Does that do anything?
No?
Click.
Click order?
Double.
Fine.
Okay.
So it hits for
10 damage.
Plus two rage.
So that kills six.
And then I will cleave into number four.
And that does just simple weapon damage, right?
Yes.
For nine.
All right, you did nine points of.
Okay, so can you just mark the damage?
Okay.
So the first six dies?
Six dies?
Oh, and I forgot to do fairy fire on him, but well.
Six dies.
And then it was number four takes nine damage.
You didn't add your plus two in rage.
For what?
Are you raging or not raging?
Do I get rage with a cleave damage too?
It's to every attack.
Okay, but I don't get my strength bonus on cleave.
Ah.
Is yeah,
that is cleave form.
I don't know if it applies or not.
Oh, yeah, let me just check.
Yes, add it.
Okay.
That seems to be the consensus.
Alright, so then that kills four as well.
And then I am adequate within attack of opportunity if those little guys come loose closer.
Alright.
Okay.
Who is up?
That was just Brewberry, right?
So it's all the wolves.
All right.
Literally all.
Let's see which wolves are still alive.
I forgot to delete a few.
So four is dead.
Four is dead?
So that's one, three, and five, right?
Yeah, so three is what?
Pardon me?
Three is technically first.
Okay, so three charges at you.
Yep, so I get an attack opportunity while he tries that.
Yes.
Okay, that's a hit for
damage.
It's another dead one.
All right.
The barbarian is getting a lot of pelts here.
Yes.
Are they fair trade pelts?
They are.
They attacked us first.
The dire wolf moves to you.
Does that give you an attack of opportunity or not?
I would have had an extra reaction, but no.
I assume it's limited to one.
Alright.
He takes a bite.
And knocks you prone for eight points of damage.
Unless you have an ability to resist prone.
While reaching,
I am large.
Ah, you're large in that case.
No, he is not prone.
You are not prone.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess I should technically be using a bigger mini.
That's fine.
I'm Maxie.
Actually, if I'm using a bigger mini, that means that my reach is even wider, isn't it?
I would say yes.
Yeah, I should be using a bigger mini.
I just read something.
We should all bow before our Halberd overlords.
Oh, geez.
20-foot reach.
No, it's still 10-foot reach.
The Halberd is still a Halberd.
It's still a 10-foot.
Later levels.
Not at this level, though.
Okay.
Actually, hold on a second.
Are we level 3 yet?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
So I have a Halberd, which is plus 5 reach, but I also have this Giant's Havoc.
My reach increases by 5.
So I actually have a 15-foot reach now.
Okay, that's good to know.
Well, that's useful.
I mean, like I said, we all bowed before our overlords.
Okay.
You got to start playing that far from it.
Alright, well, yeah, it's like.
Okay, so this guy attacks you, and this guy attacks you.
Since they're all within five feet of each other, they get to attack with advantage.
What's your armor class?
16.
Alright.
Just see what the attack bonus on this character is on the monster is.
It's a plus four, so that's a hit.
I'm done 2D20.
Keep high one plus four.
That's also a hit, so you take another 10 points of.
No, no, no.
Yes, you're 10 points of damage.
That's it.
Total of 10.
Have does five.
Well, yeah.
Yeah, half with his five.
Okay.
All the wolves.
Oh, two's dead, isn't he?
He's also.
Yes.
All right.
I should have deleted that.
Is there a button you can press to make my mini large?
Okay, thank you.
Let me just.
I think I could do something here.
This is the War of the Giants.
Okay.
Off to Soma.
It looks like it's a full action to move the moon beam, and so I'm just gonna leave it there for now.
And we're going to chew on the dire wolf first.
That's not a kill.
Alright, so I've created a giant blueberry.
Thank you.
So you should be able to drag and drop that whenever you need.
Got it.
All right.
Close in fight.
No, the second attack misses.
Dang.
All right.
So who are you attacking?
Oh, it's the dire wolf.
Alright.
So the dire wolf takes another six points of damage.
And down to 11.
Alright.
You killed another one?
Okay, we're down.
Okay, so because I see this wolf here has zero hit points.
Oh, that wasn't me.
Somebody else.
That's number four.
Yeah, four is already removed from the map.
That's okay.
Four is still on my map.
Oh, I.
Okay, so I think let's get there's only one wolf left, so let's get rid of him.
All right, he's gone.
All right.
Okay.
So we're down to one wolf.
Dave, you are no longer affected by the terror.
The pack is gone.
Dave.
Really?
Yes, yes, yes.
The pack is gone.
It's been defeated.
There's no pack left.
There's one wolf.
A wolf of one pack is not a wolf.
Okay.
All right.
Dalfine?
Can I punch her?
No, no.
It's waited until my turn.
All right, Melfino.
Okay.
One, two, three, four, five.
You don't want to go through the moon beam.
I went around it.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Yeah, I don't think it differentiates.
It's just like any creature.
I guess I could have dropped it, but sorry.
Let's see if my.
Nope.
Cannot do this easily.
That's a mess.
Right?
Booker's in Europe.
Why is that not working?
What was that?
Just ignore that.
It's just like doing some stuff.
It's just not letting me click the buttons on the page here.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm not able to click on buttons either now.
I now also have the same problem.
Still working for me, but.
Okay.
16 hits?
Yep.
Dire Wolf is 14, yeah.
15 will hit.
Okay, just so you know, today is September 2nd.
Apparently, there was a hot fix.
They're bug fixing.
Yeah, well, I need to keep working on it.
Yeah, I just want you to know.
The guy does, I did give him some money, so I will send him a note.
What, roll 20?
Okay, I did a total of 11 damage on the.
That'll take him out.
On the dire wolf.
Yeah, that'll take him out.
They're both at 11, so.
Okay, cool.
Done.
Everybody's dead?
There's one wolf left.
Rubereri needs to take care of wolf one.
No, let's make him a pet.
Tame him.
Bring back scratch.
That is a miss.
Who's next?
Wolf.
Ho-ho!
Good me.
I'll growl at the wolf.
A wolf runs.
Well, then he gets hit.
All right, well, he disengages and runs.
Oh, disengages.
Oh, he's disengaged.
But he doesn't dash, yeah.
He's done.
Guys, let him go.
All right, whatever.
All right.
Is it a rambler-looking wolf, or is it like a spectral wolf?
You've got those red eyes and shit, right?
It had like red eyes.
So you do find some pelts.
Do you wish to remove the pelts?
That is organic fair trade.
It's also blighted pelts, guys.
Well, we'll check it when we get bring it back to count.
We'll see how definitely taking the pelts.
You're going to carry that blighted pelt with you.
Yes.
I don't want that in my backpack.
You guys do what you want.
How many blighted pelts do we get?
We get five regular and one dire.
Yep.
And I have to figure out how much that's worth, but let's just make a note that you have them.
I'm going to put false for his blood.
Wow, look at that.
Where do we get to do that?
See, we can turn this into like a wolf skin cloak of displacement.
There you go.
Yeah, wow.
All right.
So I'm assuming we're back to non-giant bear blueberry.
Yes, yes.
I'll do that just to test that I know what I'm doing.
Okay, so you can, I did it for you, so you can switch to giant brewberry if you want.
You just drag him on there.
I'm just testing.
You do your thing.
All right.
So I presume you'll keep heading deeper into this bizarre forest.
That's my plan.
All right.
Okay, let me just get rid of this.
Not get lost.
All right.
Sure, why not?
You did not get lost.
All right.
There's one more.
Well, maybe I'll get lost on my own just for fun.
One good, one bad.
All right.
Let's see now.
Hold on.
Holding.
All right.
You suddenly stumble.
You suddenly, as you're walking through the forest, you step in, you see a small still pool.
And as you look at it, you don't see yourself, but twisted, distorted versions of yourselves, warped in anguish or joy.
Which one is it?
Anguish or joy?
In anguish.
Okay.
Yeah, well, it depends what you want.
So you're saying that Valfine sees a joy-ridden version of herself instead of an English-ridden one?
Yes, because that would bring her joy.
All right.
Anybody want to go for a swim?
You know, given that the trees attacked us, I don't know.
This is the center of the forest.
No, it's not, but you can sense.
How many hit points do I have?
You didn't take much.
You took like one or two shots at this time.
I'm at 16 hit points.
Let's see.
I'm going to use a bardic inspiration
on myself.
So if I fail a D20, I can benefit from it.
And yeah, why not?
I'll get in the pool.
Sure.
Unlucky would have done it.
Lucky, did you jump in the pool?
Sure.
Unlucky would have done it.
He's not here.
So for Jared.
All right, for Jared, you jump in the pool, and it's kind of like: have you seen that scene in the Marvel universe?
Okay, so basically, it's like a series of mirrors, all sort of reflecting people, scenes, faces at you all at the same time.
Okay.
Roll an intelligence saving throw.
Just the one who jumped in?
Yes, just the one who jumped in.
The creature fails a D20.
Okay.
All right.
So intelligence save.
Yes, D14.
Okay, let's see what I get.
You get an 8.
Now, hang on, it's not over yet.
You said I need a 14?
Yes.
I have a one in six chance of making it.
Let's see.
Nope.
All right.
I got a 12.
You don't notice anything, but you do gain a level of madness.
Do you want to keep looking around?
Level of madness?
This has turned into a call of Cthulhu.
Madness.
Hang on.
I'm contemplating my options.
Yeah, sure.
Why don't I use a bonus action to take another bardic inspiration, and then, sure, I'll stick around.
All right.
Okay.
You want me to roll again?
Yes.
12 and 14.
All right.
Does the madness give him a genius inspiration?
Okay.
I need to compose something right now.
This will work.
All right.
Maybe it'll mesh nicely with Velphi.
Roll a D6.
All right.
Two.
And you see a distorted
creature, human, you can't really tell, pleading.
He saw beyond, but only what he was meant to see.
The numbers, always the numbers.
It's true.
It's always the numbers.
Oh, helpful.
All right.
I think I've tested my luck enough.
I'm out.
And my madness, do you want me to roll for effect?
Yeah, roll a D100.
Roll a D100 and see what happens.
Afraid of music.
I need to compose something right now.
90.
Tariff falls unconscious.
No, when he exits the pool.
He exits the pool and just collapses.
Like, is he going to drown?
That's not so bad.
You guys can wake me up or something.
Right.
Carry you on my bare back.
All right.
So, yes, there's definitely.
You did get the impression that this was some.
Did you describe it to your friends?
Do they want to roll Arcana checks?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sure.
Once I wake up, I suppose.
How long is that going to be?
Just you slap him, he wakes up.
Okay, just in.
Yes.
I rolled an arcana check.
Thank you, Brewberry.
Hey, I can have that number.
Add us together and it's still Brewberry.
We've had Brewberry.
Can I just say Arcana chalk?
Jesus.
Can I just say something?
I don't know what it is with barbarians of this party rolling absurd dice.
It's the hot fix.
They need to fix that shit.
All right, Brewberry, tell us what it meant.
You're an expert on numbers, aren't you?
Yes.
I can count all the way to four.
One, two, four.
Three, sir.
So what you in.
So Brewberry has heard legends of these pools.
Yes.
I've heard of these pools.
They were the lore of the Earthcorp barbarians.
Yes.
Yes, that's good.
And so the key thing about these pools is that they are shadows to other places and that they appear unnaturally.
Basically, no, what you remember is that they would appear and then disappear.
And that if you looked into them, you could learn.
You had never experienced this, so this was all secondhand.
That you could, if you looked at them, you could find yourself and ask yourself some questions.
Ah.
Right.
So you jumped into the pool, so you got whatever happened.
I was expecting that.
But apparently, if you look into it, Brewberry says you can see yourself and ask yourself a question.
All right.
I'm ready to ask my question.
Okay, you're going to go do that?
All right.
Roll your wisdom saving throw.
Your intelligence saving throw, rather.
Your intelligence saving throw.
It's a good minus on that, I hope.
Should I ask my question first or should I roll my vice versa?
Yes, do whatever you want.
What side of the bread should I butter?
Bright Brewberry.
I go mad trying to figure that one out.
Why is a raven like a writing desk?
Well, Brewberry sees is a version of Brewberry that butters both sides simultaneously.
More butter.
Okay.
All right.
Roll your short-term madness effect.
This right here, this is why I'm a naturalist.
That shit ain't natural and it's messing you guys up.
Okay, so you start running away.
Does somebody want to try to grapple him?
Can I just on him?
Maybe a bear?
Yes.
All right.
I will assume you guys run.
If anybody could grapple him, it'd be me.
Yes.
You bounce on top of him.
I will just assume that Brewberry has been grappled.
He is terrified.
Minutes elapse.
Unfortunately, I have advantage on grapple.
Do it.
All right.
Okay, so we could do this a few times.
Roll.
Let's keep rolling.
All right, fine.
We're going to do a pursuit.
We're going to do a chase.
Oh, I rolled pretty fast.
That's good.
What did you roll?
Roll strength or what?
Yeah, strength or acrobatics or athletics.
Oh, acrobatics or athletics.
I'm not really good at either.
Bear, though, you should be good at it.
I don't get extra abilities that I see.
Oh, I do.
I guess acrobatics is decks, so I get a plus zero anyway.
Yeah, that's fine.
Well, I do win that fight.
Stay down, Brewberry.
This is for your own good.
All right.
I was going to go do the chase rules, but you know.
Bear wins.
Right.
Bruberry's kind of like screaming about, you know, there's no right side.
That's actually not what it said, but you know, that's what you think you saw.
Okay.
All right.
So Valfine will ask a more intelligent question.
Nice.
Stop.
For your own sanity.
Aren't we supposed to ask him?
I can just cast lesser restoration on him, right?
But I have to touch him for that, don't I?
Yes.
Well, if you're touching them, you can, you know.
I want to burn a spell on this.
Yes.
If we're having trouble grappling him, are we having trouble?
No, no.
Bruberry is like at some point in time, Bruberry just stops a bit.
He gave up under weight of bear.
Brewberry's trying to explain to Valfina to Soma the importance of, but that it's not one side, but both sides.
All right.
Good, good barbarian.
Both sides.
So not one.
I understand.
We'll get you both sides of your bread.
We'll cut the crusts off, too.
But I assume this has something to do with how we, you know, the source of this thing, and so therefore we should still be interacting with it.
Yes?
You can come back.
Let's go to the center.
Anyway, what was no, it's not the center.
The center is not at the center of the forest yet.
Oh, okay.
So one by one, I'm watching my compatriots go mad.
So, you know.
So do you guys wait to get to?
I presume you're going to go to the center.
Let's head to the center.
All right.
Yeesh.
That looks like a good place to stop.
Yes.
This is a good place to stop.
And there's more of those wells.
Oh, there are.
Yes.
So you guys can go mad to your heart's content.
Right.
So these are.
So yes, the point here is so that you know what these are all wells.
Just so we're.
Wait, they're all wells or just the blue ones are wells.
This is a well.
Sorry.
They're just very oh, the sun spots or whatever.
Yeah, that was what the icon was supposed to be.
I just anyway, yeah, I get you.
It will.
Which if we go in from the northwest, looks like we can avoid the brambles.
Right.
Anyway, so we will discuss it.
And I will, we will, I just, yes, you arrive here.
Um, do you want to be going from the north?
I mean, you can pick which.
I'll just drop you in here.
You guys.
It looks like we want to come in from the northwest to avoid the brambles.
And I didn't put these here, but you also see a druid and two folks who look like rangers caught in the brambles.
Oh, the first party.
Oh, well, once we save them, then they can do the battle.
Excellent.
We can go get all the credit.
Put them in the front.
Yes, exactly.
All right.
And when they do look, what's the word I'm looking for?
Druish.
Well, definitely Druidish.
But definitely, you know, Soma recognizes them as members of the Emerald Enclave.
Well, it's great.
Time to get some more allies.
We're all going to be partying, playing music together, and this is all over.
Okay.
Listening to your music together.
All right.
I will exit here.
All right, guys.
See you next week.
Bye.